

STUDENT · UNDERGRAD

15, Jagdish Colony, Mahesh Nagar, Jaipur

□ (+91) 882-407-1985 | **S**akshi30301@gmail.com | **S**akshiAgarwal30301 | **S**akshi-agarwal

Summary_

A person with a strong interest in software programs, strong communication and analytical abilities, and a desire to apply technical expertise to meet the demands of the firm I. I want to collaborate with a variety of people and develop as a technical expert and a professional software developer.

Work Experience

Utkarshini Edutech

Game Development Intern

July 2021 - August. 2021

- Development of Games for learning based on PyGame
- Responsible for creation of descriptions in Jupyter Notebook

Lets Grow More

Web Developer Intern. Sept. 2021 - Oct. 2021

- worked on progressive web app
- created reusable react components, using ant design and moduler css.
- designed and developed a full stack project

Competitions and Personal Projects.

Global Hackathon

Bus Management System April 2022

- A bus management system with features i.e. Authentication, Live Tracking, Routing, Leaderboard etc.
- Implemented in flutter and Material UI and Used Google Maps

Responsive Website

CREATED A DYNAMIC WEBSITE USING WORDPRESS

Apr. 2022 - May. 2022

- created dynamic components of site using CSS and JavaScript
- · experimented with new front end technologies

Python Based Games

CREATED A FEW GAMES BASED ON PYTHON AND HOSTED THEM ON A WEBSITE

Nov. 2021 - Feb. 2022

- used Pygame and other librarries to develop the game
- used wordpress and git for developing the website

Skills

Front-end React, HTML5, CSS, Javascript

Programming C, JAVA, SQL, LaTeX

Proficient Tools Microsoft VS Code, Android Studio, Canva, Figma, MS Office

Interests Exploring New Tech, Badminton, Design, Music

Languages Hindi, English

Education

Swami Keshvanand Institute of Technology

Jaipui

B.Tech in Information Technology

Mar. 2019 - Aug. 2023

• will graduate in 2023

Tilak Public School

• Cummulative CGPA 9.58

Jaipur

Apr. 2017 - Mar. 2019

P.C.M.

• Cummulative percentage 80.60%

SAKSHI AGARWAL · RÉSUMÉ